streamlineicons.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Streamline Icons

### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To improve our website. (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 

\- To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our policy is located at .

### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at 

<http://www.streamlineicons.com/privacy-policy.html>

### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.   

Suite 2611 Langham Place Office Tower  
Kowloon 23514 - Hong-Kong   
Hong-Kong
